<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
  <rss xmlns:joblisting="http://www.neogov.com/namespaces/JobListing" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel xmlns:joblisting="http://www.neogov.com/namespaces/JobListing" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

      <title>State of Michigan, MI</title>
      <atom:link href="http://agency.governmentjobs.com/michigan/default.cfm?format=xml&amp;promotionaljobs=0&amp;transfer=0" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
      <link>http://agency.governmentjobs.com/michigan</link>
      <description>Latest Employment Information</description>
      <language>en-us</language>
      <ttl>360</ttl>
      <generator>www.neogov.com</generator>
      <joblisting:timeZone>Eastern Time (US &amp; Canada)</joblisting:timeZone>
      <joblisting:UTCOffset>-5.00</joblisting:UTCOffset>

        <item xmlns:joblisting="http://www.neogov.com/namespaces/JobListing" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
          <title>Information Technology Programmer Analyst</title>
          <link>http://agency.governmentjobs.com/michigan/default.cfm?action=viewjob&amp;jobid=386302</link>
          <pubdate>2012-03-12 10:16:56.14</pubdate>
          <description>&lt;font face=&quot;Arial&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: small&quot;&gt;The job duties listed are typical examples of the work performed by positions in this job classification.&amp;nbsp; Not all duties assigned to every position are included, nor is it expected that all positions will be assigned every duty.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Writes, compiles, and modifies applications programs for computerized systems and keys into program code.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Develops or acquires test data and runs tests to determine the accuracy of program logic to produce desired results; debugs and revises programs based on test results.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Uses program specifications to prepare the logic sequence of program source statements in the development, modification, documentation, and maintenance of computer programs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Develops and prepares documents for the general design of solutions that meet system and security requirements, including the selection of alternative approaches.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Develops applications to be used in client server environments.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Develops and maintains automated data processing systems and computer application programs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Develops specifications to detail what new systems or enhancements to existing systems can accomplish.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Develops specifications for databases, communication systems, hardware, network, security, storage and software configurations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Develops operation and installation procedures for communication systems, hardware, network, security, storage and software.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Serves as liaison with users concerning requests, usage, standards, security, and other developmental and production matters.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Develops structured diagrams for the specifications of databases, communication systems, computer or storage area networks, security or network programs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Develops, compiles, maintains and documents configurations of the following:&amp;nbsp; databases, servers, computers, security and network monitor systems, packaged programs, macros, utilities, and communication systems.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Develops guidelines and upgrade techniques of new operational procedures for the support of databases, hardware systems, operating systems software, network systems software, security and client server systems.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Develops and implements databases, communication systems, storage area networks, security and applications with user departments, vendors, and data centers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Develops and implements the directory configurations, messaging configurations, and state-wide operation systems which include communication systems (servers, routers, switches and hubs).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Develops the gateways, filters and interfaces related to state-wide messaging and communication systems.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Develops detailed systems operations designs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Tests programs and systems and integrates system modules.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Converts and implements new systems or upgrades existing systems.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Develops, implements, and monitors information technology quality assurance standards.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Develops cost estimates for systems development and upgrades to existing systems.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Evaluates network services equipment and software for purchase; recommends new configurations, provides training or arranges for vendor training for system users.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Evaluates, implements, and provides customer support for third-party software systems in a client server environment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Maintains records and prepares reports and correspondence related to the work.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Performs related duties as assigned.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/font&gt;</description>
          <joblisting:jobNumberSingle>0801-2012-CONTITPA</joblisting:jobNumberSingle>
          <joblisting:jobId>386302</joblisting:jobId>
          <joblisting:advertiseFromDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011</joblisting:advertiseFromDate>
          <joblisting:advertiseToDateTime>Continuous</joblisting:advertiseToDateTime>
          <joblisting:advertiseFromDateUTC>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 05:00:00</joblisting:advertiseFromDateUTC>
          <joblisting:advertiseToDateTimeUTC>Continuous</joblisting:advertiseToDateTimeUTC>
          <joblisting:minimumSalary>17.4</joblisting:minimumSalary>
          <joblisting:maximumSalary>31.91</joblisting:maximumSalary>
          <joblisting:salaryCurrency>USD</joblisting:salaryCurrency>
          <joblisting:salaryInterval>Hour</joblisting:salaryInterval>
          <joblisting:jobType>Permanent Full Time</joblisting:jobType>
          <joblisting:location>Various</joblisting:location>
          <joblisting:state>Michigan</joblisting:state>
          <joblisting:department>Technology, Management and Budget</joblisting:department>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://agency.governmentjobs.com/michigan/default.cfm?action=viewjob&amp;jobid=386302</guid>
          <categories>
                <category xmlns:joblisting="http://www.neogov.com/namespaces/JobListing" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
                  <CategoryCode>ITandComputers</CategoryCode>
                  <Category>IT and Computers</Category>
                </category>
                <category xmlns:joblisting="http://www.neogov.com/namespaces/JobListing" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
                  <CategoryCode>Professional</CategoryCode>
                  <Category>Professional</Category>
                </category>
          </categories>
        </item>

    </channel>
  </rss>
